amenclinics.com 2014-04-07

# Amen Clinics | Brain Imaging, Therapy, and Treatments

Amen Clinics, Inc. values the privacy of all of our readers. We take very seriously the need to respect and protect your privacy and the security of any information you may share with us. We’ve built a site that allows you to control how much information you give us and how that information is used. This privacy policy (“Policy”) describes the data collection, use, and disclosure practices of Amen Clinics, Inc. in connection with the Web Site, www.AmenClinics.com (the “Web Site” or “Site”).

This Policy applies to information collected only directly through or from AmenClinics.com. This Policy also does not apply to third-party online resources to which AmenClinics.com may link, because Amen Clinics, Inc. does not control their content or their privacy practices.

Please read our Policy carefully. Your understanding of how we use any information you provide — and your trust that we will use it carefully — are very important both to you and to us. Why? Because it helps us provide more relevant, useful information to you. If you have any questions about our data collection, use, or disclosure practices, please contact us in any of the ways listed at the end (Section 17). Please also be sure to read our complete Terms of Use.

  1. ### What Information Do We Collect?

AmenClinics.com’s purpose is to provide you with detailed healthcare information so we may request correspondingly detailed personal health information from you. Certain information is necessary for us to provide one or more services to you. For a full description of these services, see Section 4, “How We Use the Information We Collect.” Other information is optional; if you elect not to provide optional information, it may limit the value of what AmenClinics.com can provide for you. For example, if we do not have information on a mental health condition you may have — such as attention deficit disorder (ADD) — we will not be able to provide information about how best to manage your diet and lifestyle to improve your health. (That includes information on medications that may help you manage a diagnosed condition like ADD.) In short, the more information we have about you, the more valuable AmenClinics.com can be to you.

We collect two types of information on AmenClinics.com. The first, “Personal Information,” is information that allows someone to identify or contact you, such as your name and e-mail address, as well as any information about you that is associated with or linked to any of the foregoing information. The second type, “Anonymous Data,” is data not associated with or linked to your Personal Information. Anonymous Data cannot be used to identify you. We collect Personal Information and Anonymous Data based on your participation on AmenClinics.com.

  2. ### How We Collect Information from You

AmenClinics.com will collect information from you when you interact with us in the following ways:

**a) Cookies**  

As with most sites on the Internet, when you visit our Site, AmenClinics.com may place a “cookie” on your computer that enables us to give you a better experience on the Site.

    * Internet cookies are small text files that save data about you as an individual visitor and help AmenClinics.com deliver personalized content and other services in a manner convenient to you. When you first register or sign in, AmenClinics.com places your member ID and e-mail address into a cookie file.
    * If you select “Remember Me” when signing up or signing in, AmenClinics.com also places your e-mail address and password into another, separate cookie file.
    * Many Web browsers are automatically set to accept cookies. You may change your browser settings to either reject cookies or notify you when a cookie is about to be placed on your computer. Please note, however, that rejecting cookies while visiting AmenClinics.com may result in certain parts of the Site not operating correctly or as efficiently as they would with cookies. For example, if you are a AmenClinics.com Member without a cookie, you may need to enter your username and password each time you visit the Site in order to see your AmenClinics.com calculation. If you allow cookies, it streamlines your user experience on AmenClinics.com and keeps track of your preferences.
**b) IP Address**

An “IP Address” is actually a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you use the Internet. In some cases, your IP address stays the same from session to session; but if you use a consumer Internet access provider (such as Earthlink or AT&T), your IP address probably varies from session to session. We track IP addresses solely in conjunction with session cookies to analyze our Web page flow.

**Other Systems**

Information is also collected from you when:

    * You fill out forms on our Site, including registration forms, the AmenClinics.com tests, tools, and assessments.
    * You interact with the message boards and post comments on articles.
    * You click on advertisements on the Site or in one of the free health newsletters and e-mails you receive from AmenClinics.com.
    * You invite someone else to join AmenClinics.com through our Web Site’s sharing tools — in that case, we will collect your name and e-mail address, as well as the other person’s e-mail address, in order to send this e-mail; if you decide to invite someone else to take the AmenClinics.com tests and they subsequently register with us, we will collect and save the other person’s e-mail address, as we would for anyone who registers on the Site.

Also, in most instances we include certain tracking links that allow us to monitor whether you accessed specific content or advertisements. If you click on one of these links, we will record that click and certain activities on AmenClinics.com associated with that tracking link. We may use this information for various purposes, such as to conduct internal research on our users’ demographics, interests, and clicking behavior and to customize the content and advertisements you see.

  3. ### How We Use the Information We Collect

When you register with AmenClinics.com, we use your Personal Information to create a customized Web experience for you and to improve our services. We may use Personal Information to:

    * Determine your brain type and process your answers to quizzes in ways that provide you with tailored information regarding your health.
    * Present you with advertising on the Site, based on the health interests you listed in Personal Information.
    * Improve the content and layout of AmenClinics.com.
    * Statistically analyze user behavior.
    * Receive feedback on editorial content.
    * Develop products, marketing, and promotions internally at AmenClinics.com.
    * Contact you regarding your account status or changes to our Terms and Conditions, including our Privacy Policy.
    * Merging your Registration Information with other, optional types of Personal Information that you provide to us voluntarily, such as merging your health-related information from taking the AmenClinics.com tests with your responses to surveys, health assessments, and questionnaires. In other words, we will combine basic Registration Information you provide to us (e-mail address, username, password, age, gender, and zip code) with additional information you provide.
    * Combining your Personal Information with outside records, such as postal data and other demographic data. We do this to conduct research, improve the quality of our services, and send you printed health and wellness information by postal mail that we believe may be of interest to you.
    * Participating in market research activities through AmenClinics.com, including health surveys. When you take part in such activities, we may ask you to submit Personal Information such as health and lifestyle data about you and your family. However, our reports and analyses to clients and partners are made only on an anonymous basis, using Anonymous Data.

We do not send or support the delivery of unsolicited bulk e-mail (a.k.a. “spam”).

  4. ### Your Choices Regarding Your Personal Data

As a convenience to our Members, we provide a number of ways to review and change information in your account and to unsubscribe from AmenClinics.com services. For one, you can go to the AmenClinics.com and log onto your account page to make any desired changes. Similarly, each e-mail message you receive from us contains one or more links to AmenClinics.com that allow you to conveniently access this information. Or you can unsubscribe at any time by clicking here.

  5. ### Blogs, Videos, and Other User-Generated Postings; Social Networking

If you choose to post material to any blogs or forums, participate in our social networking channels, or in any other community features that may be offered from time to time on our Sites, you will be solely responsible for all content, messages, text, files, images, graphics, photos, audio clips, sounds, videos, or other materials (the “Postings”). You agree and warrant that any Postings you make on the Site will be true and accurate, will not defame any person or invade any person’s privacy, and will not infringe upon the proprietary rights of any person. You agree not to make any Postings to which you do not own the rights. By making Postings, you understand and acknowledge that visitors to AmenClinics.com may post comments about your Postings which may be derogatory, and that AmenClinics.com has no obligation to monitor or delete any such comments. You also acknowledge that any information you may receive from another advice-giver on our Site is not a substitute for professional medical information or advice and is governed by the disclaimers and limitations set forth in our Terms of Use.

AmenClinics.com reserves the right, but has no obligation, to monitor Postings. AmenClinics.com does not and cannot monitor all of the Postings made to the Sites and will not be responsible for the content of any Postings. AmenClinics.com has no obligation to verify the accuracy of any personally identifying information posted to our Sites. However, AmenClinics.com reserves the right to delete any material in any Posting that is obscene, harassing, offensive, or otherwise objectionable and not in keeping with the community standards of AmenClinics.com. Under no circumstances will AmenClinics.com be liable for any inaccuracy or defect in any Postings. We also expect our users to adhere to certain rules. Therefore, you agree not to post, e-mail, or otherwise make available Postings:

    * That are unlawful, harmful, threatening, abusive, harassing, defamatory, pornographic, libelous, or invasive of another’s privacy or harmful to minors in any way.
    * That harass, degrade, intimidate, or are hateful toward an individual or group of individuals on the basis of religion, gender, sexual orientation, race, ethnicity, age, or disability.
    * That include personal or identifying information about another person without that person’s explicit consent.
    * That are false, deceptive, misleading, deceitful, misinformative, constitute “bait and switch,” or impersonate any person or entity.
    * That contain your own or a third party’s advertising, branding, or promotional content.
    * That infringe upon any proprietary rights, including copyright, of any party, or Postings that you do not have a right to make available.
    * That restrict or inhibit any other user from using and enjoying AmenClinics.com or the AmenClinics.com services offered on them.

Because AmenClinics.com does not monitor the Postings, you agree to use and rely on them at your own risk. AmenClinics.com cannot make any representation or warranty about the material contained in the Postings. AmenClinics.com likewise assumes no responsibility for any contact you may have with other users of our Sites, either online or offline. If you elect to meet in person with someone you may meet on our Sites, you do so at your own risk; under no circumstances will AmenClinics.com be liable for any activity or injury that may occur.

  6. ### Legal Disclosure

AmenClinics.com may disclose information about you and your use of the AmenClinics.com and the AmenClinics.com services if AmenClinics.com believes such disclosure is reasonably necessary in order to:

(i) Comply with the law or legal process where a formal request has been made, such as from an administrative oversight agency, civil suit, subpoena, court order, or judicial or administrative proceeding;

(ii) Protect or defend the rights or property of AmenClinics.com or others;

(iii) Enforce the AmenClinics.com Terms and Conditions or this Privacy Policy;

(iv) Respond to claims that the content(s) of a communication violates the rights of another.

Also, circumstances may arise where, for business reasons, AmenClinics.com may decide to reorganize, or divest all or part of its business through sale, assignment, merger, or acquisition. In these circumstances, personal information may be shared with the actual or prospective purchasers or assignees. In such an event, we shall provide notice of any material change to this Privacy Policy, or our services, in the manner described in the Updates section of this Privacy Policy (see Section 16).

  7. ### Sweepstakes, Give-Aways, and Contests

We may conduct give-aways, contests, and other promotions on the Site in which we may ask you for additional information. We will use and treat this information as Personal Information in accordance with the terms of this Policy. Participation in such give-aways and contests is not necessary to use AmenClinics.com, and whether you may choose to participate in any particular give-away or contest or not will not affect your general use of the Site.

  8. ### Security

AmenClinics.com has implemented security measures intended to prevent the loss, misuse, or alteration of the information under its control. Our network access to the infrastructure is protected by a firewall protection system. Member information is backed up on a periodic basis to protect against accidental loss. You have the option when you enter personally identifiable information (e.g., registration, health profile questions, surveys) to use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption to protect your information during its transmission across the Internet. We use secure digital certificates to assist with verification that you’re actually using AmenClinics.com and have not been diverted to an imposter Web site.

However, we cannot guarantee that communications between you and AmenClinics.com will not be intercepted by others, and that information stored on our servers will be free from unauthorized access. While we have taken reasonable precautions to protect this information, you should always use discretion in what information you send to us and not expect that such information will be absolutely free from intrusion. The confidentiality of any communication or material transmitted to or from AmenClinics.com cannot be and is not guaranteed. Accordingly, AmenClinics.com is not responsible for the security of information transmitted via the Internet.

### About Our Affiliates

AmenClinics.com is a wholly owned subsidiary of Amen Clinics. Inc. These are our current Affiliates (we may add additional Affiliates in the future; if we do, they will be posted here and on the Site, but the addition of new Affiliates shall not be deemed to necessitate a change to this Privacy Policy)

  9. ### Children

AmenClinics.com services and Web Sites are not directed at children. They are designed for individuals who are 20 years of age or older. We will not request or knowingly collect information from an individual under age 20.

If you are a parent and you’re worried about your children’s activities or their privacy on our Site, we encourage you to e-mail us at [privacy@amenclinic.com](mailto:privacy@amenclinic.com) [privacy@amenclinic.com](mailto:privacy@amenclinic.com).

  10. ### A Note to Non-U.S. Users

YOU EXPRESSLY CONSENT TO THE PROCESSING OF YOUR PERSONAL DATA IN ACCORDANCE WITH THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT. YOUR PERSONAL DATA MAY BE PROCESSED IN THE UNITED STATES. UNITED STATES LAWS REGARDING PROCESSING OF PERSONAL DATA MAY BE LESS STRINGENT THAN THE LAWS IN YOUR COUNTRY.

  11. ### A Note to California and Canada Users

California and Canada residents have the right to know how their information may be shared with third parties who engage in direct marketing activities; this Privacy Policy explains our practices and how you can opt out of having your information shared for such purposes.

  12. ### Updates

AmenClinics.com reserves the right, at any time and without notice, to add to, update, change, modify, or revise this Privacy Policy or our services simply by posting such change, update, or modification on the Web Site. Any such addition, update, change, modification, or revision will be effective immediately upon posting on the Web Site. Upon any material change to this Privacy Policy, or our services, we may also notify you by notification on the Site and/or notification delivered by e-mail if you are a current AmenClinics.com Member with a valid, deliverable e-mail address at the time of the material change. If you do not accept the terms of this Policy, we ask that you do not register with AmenClinics.com.

  13. ### Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Web Site, or your dealings with AmenClinics.com, you can contact:  
**Amen Clinics, Inc.**  
4019 Westerly Place, #100  
Newport Beach, CA 92660 USA  
(888) 564-2700
